Combinar, vá se foder!
Amemiya Akira
You've got some nerve coming out here
Into the eye of the storm
with a noose 'round your neck
Knowing that you're going to be dead
What's mine is mine, what's yours is mine
No choice in matter everything's fine
If you stay where you were
Obey  Don't think  Consume
Don't even start to assume
I know I got what you need
Evacuate to the underground
This is no place for you
I know I got what you need
I know I got it but its MINE
You've got some nerve coming out here
Into the eye of the storm
with a noose 'round your neck
Audacity at its best
You've got no place to run
You've got no place to hide
Your smell is groping my tongue
Obey  Don't think  Consume
The sign is right in front of you
I know I got what you need
It doesn't mean a thing to me
You've been warned
And I'm out on the kill